// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "On what day is Jamaican Independence observed each year?", 
    answer: "August 6 (or, in case it falls on a Sunday, then the following day)",
    options: [
         "The first Monday of August",
         "August 6 (or, in case it falls on a Sunday, then the following day)",
         "August 7",
         "Government decides on a date each year"
    ]
},
{
    numb: 2,
    question: "Who is Jamaica’s first National Hero?", 
    answer: "Marcus Garvey",
    options: [
         "Alexander Bustamante",
         "Bob Marley",
         "Marcus Garvey",
         "Nanny of the Maroons"
    ]
},
{
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which National Hero was the leader of Morant Bay Rebellion?", 
    answer: "Paul Bogle",
    options: [
         "Paul Bogle",
         "Nanny of the Maroons",
         "Sam Sharpe",
         "George William Gordon "
    ]
},
{
    numb: 4,
    question: "Who represented The Queen at Jamaica’s Independence celebrations in 1962?", 
    answer: "Princess Margaret",
    options: [
         "No one, Queen Elizabeth II was present at the celebration",
         "Princess Margaret",
         "Governor General, Sir Kenneth Blackburne",
         "Prince Philip"
    ]
},
{
    numb: 5,
    question: "What is the National Bird?", 
    answer: "‘Doctor Bird’",
    options: [
         "Chicken",
         "‘Doctor Bird’",
         "John Crow",
         "Yellow-billed Parrot"
    ]
}, 
{
    numb: 6,
    question: "What is Jamaica’s National Fruit?",
    answer: "Ackee",
    options: [
         "Ackee",
         "Jamaica does not have a National Fruit",
         "Pineapple",
         "Mango"
    ]
},
{
    numb: 7,
    question: "Bob Marley lived in… when he met 'The Wailers'", 
    answer: "Trench Town, Kingston",
    options: [
         "Morant Bay, St Thomas",
         "Nine Mile, St Ann",
         "Trench Town, Kingston",
         "Oracabessa, St Mary"
    ]
},
{
    numb: 8,
    question: "Which one of the following is not a code for use of the Jamaican Flag?",
    answer: "All of the above are codes for use of the Jamaican flag.",
    options: [
         "The Jamaican flag should never be allowed to touch the ground or floor.",
         "When the flag becomes worn and must be replaced, it should be burnt privately",
         "All of the above are codes for use of the Jamaican flag.",
         "The flag should never be smaller than any other flag flown at the same time."
    ]
},
{
    numb: 9,
    question: "Who was Jamaica’s first Prime Minister?",
    answer: "Alexander Bustamante",
    options: [
         "Norman Manley",
         "Alexander Bustamante",
         "Michael Manley",
         "Donald Sangster"
    ]
},
{
    numb: 10,
    question: "Who are believed to be the original inhabitants of Jamaica?",
    answer: "Tainos",
    options: [
         "Africans",
         "Tainos",
         "Caribs",
         "The Spanish"
    ]
},
{
    numb: 11,
    question: "Where in Jamaica was infamously known as the ‘wickedest city on Earth’?", 
    answer: "Port Royal",
    options: [
         "Tivoli Gardens",
         "De La Vega City",
         "Port Royal",
         "Cherry Gardens"
    ]
},
{ 
    numb: 12,
    question: "What high school did Usain Bolt attend?",
    answer: "William Knibb",
    options: [
         "Munro",
         "Calabar",
         "Kingston College",
         "William Knibb"
    ]
},
{
    numb: 13,
    question: "Who won the first Festival Song Competition in 1966?",
    answer: "The Maytals – ‘Bam Bam’",
    options: [
         " Eric Donaldson – ‘Cherry Oh Baby’",
         "The Maytals – ‘Bam Bam’",
         "The Jamaicans – ‘Ba Ba Boom’",
         "Roy Rayon – ‘Give Thanks and Praises’"
    ]
},
{        
    numb: 14,
    question: "How many parishes are in Jamaica?", 
    answer: "14",
    options: [
         "10",
         "12",
         "14",
         "15"
    ]
},
{        
    numb: 15,
    question: "Which parish is known as the “bread basket parish”?", 
    answer: "St Elizabeth",
    options: [
         "St Elizabeth",
         "St Ann",
         "Portland",
         "St. Thomas"
    ]
},
{        
    numb: 16,
    question: "What was the capital city of Jamaica immediately before Kingston became capital in 1872?", 
    answer: "Spanish Town",
    options: [
         "Montego Bay",
         "Spanish Town",
         "Port Royal",
         "Seville"
    ]
},
{        
    numb: 17,
    question: "Who was the first Jamaican woman to win an Olympic Gold medal?", 
    answer: "Deon Hemmings McCatty",
    options: [
         "Veronica Campbell Brown",
         "Deon Hemmings McCatty",
         "Grace Jackson",
         "Merlene Ottey"
    ]
},
{        
    numb: 18,
    question: "Who won the first Grammy Award for Best Reggae Album?", 
    answer: "Black Uhuru – ‘Anthem’",
    options: [
         "Black Uhuru – ‘Anthem’",
         "Bob Marley – ‘Legend’",
         "Shabba Ranks – ‘As Raw As Ever’",
         "Ziggy Marley and the Melody Makers – ‘Conscious Party’"
    ]
},
{        
    numb: 19,
    question: "Who scored Jamaica’s first ever win, in a FIFA World Cup Match?", 
    answer: "Theodore Whitmore",
    options: [
         "Theodore Whitmore",
         "Robbie Earle",
         "Walter Boyd",
         "Deon Burton"
    ]
},
{        
    numb: 20,
    question: "Who was the first Jamaican to win the Miss World contest?", 
    answer: "Carole Joan Crawford",
    options: [
         "Lisa Hanna",
         "Carole Joan Crawford",
         "Cindy Breakspeare",
         "Yendi Phillipps"
    ]
},
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];